http://www.naturalsofashland.com/pages/privacy-security

Updated May 24, 2018
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.naturals-inc.com/ (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies: - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. - “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, PayPal order information, Amazon Pay order information), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns), and for advertising and retargeting.
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by: FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads MAILCHIMP - https://naturals-inc.us11.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=012351cda5be44ba7630a71d5&id=9b77935eda
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
MAILING LIST
You will receive newsletters or promotional notices via email from us only if you have asked to be on our mailing list. Each time you receive an email from Naturals Inc., you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" or stop receiving them. Simply follow the instructions at the end of each email message to be removed from our mailing list. Or, visit: https://naturals-inc.us11.list-manage.com/unsubscribe?u=012351cda5be44ba7630a71d5&id=9b77935eda
If you wish to update, revise or delete any of the contact information we have collected, click on “Update Your Preferences” in the footer of any email from Naturals Inc. and change the information yourself, or contact us at: info@naturals-inc.com, explaining your request.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
MINORS
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of thirteen.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
SECURITY
We have taken every measure to ensure that online shopping is as secure as ordering from a catalog or buying from a store. We secure your private information using the trusted Shopify SSL Certificate. Secure Socket Layering (SSL) is the industry standard encryption technology that ensures safe Internet transmission of your personal information. The secure mode begins when you initiate an order. You will know you are in secure mode when the tiny padlock icon, located at the bottom of your browser, appears as "locked." You can also verify you are in secure mode by looking at the URL line of your browser. When the letters "http" change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you're about to enter a secure area. When you enter your personal information into the order form, it is scrambled, transmitted across the Internet, then decoded when it gets to us. All information is stored in a secure server and can only be accessed by employees authorized to process your orders.
Naturals guarantees that every online transaction is 100% safe. If unauthorized charges appear on your credit card as a result of shopping with us while using our secure server, we will reimburse you up to the maximum £35.49 legal liability. We only require that you follow the reporting steps required by the issuer of your card (under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than £35.49 of fraudulent charges).
Making a credit card purchase is just as safe on our Web site as it is by telephone, but if you prefer the latter, you may purchase online merchandise by calling toll-free 1·866·482·1119. Please call during the hours of Mon-Fri, 9am-3pm PST. One of our customer service associates will gladly take your order.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@naturals-inc.com or by mail using the details provided below:
Call our toll free number: 1·866·482·1119
For customers outside of the US: 1·541·482·1119
Email us at: info@naturals-inc.com
Write to us at:
Naturals Inc.
1654 Williams Hwy.
Enter your email address to receive updates and special offers from Naturals Inc.
© 2017 Naturals Inc. Women's Clothing and Accessories by Eileen Fisher, Three Dots and Raffaello Rossi, All Rights Reserved.
ecommerce by
port80
Search our store
